MARRIAGE MIXER
خلاط الزواج
You're Ami Shirakawa?
هل أنت عامي شيراكاوا؟
Hinako Shinoda.
هيناكو شينودا.
Is it okay if I tell Niko-chan your name?
هل من المقبول أن أخبر نيكو تشان باسمك؟
Yes.
نعم.
You'll probably be wearing name tags,
من المحتمل أن ترتدي بطاقات تحمل أسماء،
so let's have her approach you.
لذا دعنا نجعلها تقترب منك.
Okay.
تمام.
That's pretty vague.
هذا غامض جدًا.
Will this work out?
هل سينجح هذا الأمر؟
I'll let her know.
سأخبرها.
You're Makiko Tanioka?
هل أنت ماكيكو تانيوكا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Thank you for coming today.
شكرا لحضورك اليوم.
Ms. Tanioka? Ms. Makiko Tanioka?
سيدة تانياكا؟ السيدة ماكيكو تانيوكا؟
You left your bag.
لقد تركت حقيبتك.
I'm so sorry!
أنا آسف جدا!
The third victim is Makiko Tanioka, age 28.
الضحية الثالثة هي ماكيكو تانيوكا، 28 عامًا.
Could I ask you a question?
هل يمكنني أن أسألك سؤالا؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
When did you get today's ticket?
متى حصلت على التذكرة اليوم؟
In April.
في شهر أبريل.
That's a while ago.
لقد كان ذلك منذ فترة طويلة.
Every member does.
كل عضو يفعل ذلك.
It's so popular it fills up right away.
إنها مشهورة جدًا لدرجة أنها تمتلئ على الفور.
I suppose so.
أعتقد ذلك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
KUWABARA GOOD LUCK
حظ سعيد
Right, I'm supposed to meet with this anonymous Niko-chan.
حسنًا، من المفترض أن أقابل هذا نيكو تشان المجهول.
What was their relationship to the late Ms. Tanioka?
ما هي علاقتهم بالسيدة تانيوكا المرحومة؟
A close friend, apparently.
صديق مقرب، على ما يبدو.
Ms. Tanioka entrusted something to Niko-chan before she died.
لقد عهدت السيدة تانيوكا بشيء إلى نيكو تشان قبل وفاتها.
My job is to meet them in person to find out what.
وظيفتي هي مقابلتهم شخصيًا لمعرفة ما يلي.
Sounds like you got stuck with another tough assignment.
يبدو أنك قد واجهت مهمة صعبة أخرى.
It's like the epitome of a Sengoku Weekly job.
إنه مثل نموذج لوظيفة Sengoku Weekly.
Well, I've been lying low so nobody finds out I'm a reporter.
حسنًا، لقد كنت أختبئ حتى لا يكتشف أحد أنني مراسل.
What if the killer is watching you right now, though?
ماذا لو كان القاتل يراقبك الآن؟
Then I'd get killed next.
ثم سأقتل بعد ذلك.
I'll do my best.
سأبذل قصارى جهدي.
Bye.
الوداع.
Okay!
تمام!
Niko-chan.
نيكو تشان.
They're taking so long.
إنهم يأخذون وقتا طويلا.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
What do you look like?
ماذا تشبه؟
What do I do? I can't just wait here for them the whole time.
ماذا أفعل؟ لا أستطيع الانتظار هنا طوال الوقت.
I'll have them make an announcement!
سأطلب منهم الإعلان عن ذلك!
Wait, hold on.
انتظر، انتظر.
That would draw attention.
وهذا من شأنه أن يلفت الانتباه.
"Niko-chan, please come to the reception counter."
"نيكو-تشان، من فضلك تعالي إلى مكتب الاستقبال."
What if a lot of people gather?
ماذا لو تجمع عدد كبير من الناس؟
I don't know what they look like.
لا أعرف كيف يبدوا.
That won't work.
هذا لن ينجح.
I can check everyone's name tags
أستطيع التحقق من بطاقات أسماء الجميع
and find someone who might be called Niko-chan.
والعثور على شخص يمكن أن يسمى نيكو تشان.
Wait, nicknames aren't that simple.
انتظر، الألقاب ليست بهذه البساطة.
Maybe the nickname comes from their smile.
ربما يأتي اللقب من ابتسامتهم.
Do I need to make everyone smile then?
هل يجب علي أن أجعل الجميع يبتسمون إذن؟
I can't do that.
لا أستطيع فعل ذلك.
I could pretend to call out to someone
أستطيع أن أتظاهر بأنني أدعو شخصًا ما
and just shout out "Niko-chan!"
وصرخ فقط "نيكو تشان!"
No, it would suck if nobody answered.
لا، سيكون الأمر سيئًا إذا لم يجيب أحد.
Everyone would look at me at once
الجميع سوف ينظرون إلي في وقت واحد
and kick me out for acting crazy.
وطردني بسبب تصرفي المجنون.
What do I do?
ماذا أفعل؟
Niko-chan!
نيكو تشان!
The Incident Team is trying to track down Kubozuka,
يحاول فريق الحادث تعقب كوبوزوكا،
but we're not having any luck.
ولكننا لم نحصل على أي حظ.
Just sent it.
لقد أرسلته للتو.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
What photos are these?
ما هذه الصور؟
It's an industry party.
إنه حفل صناعي.
From stylists like me, to photographers, designers, and aspiring models
من المصممين مثلي، إلى المصورين والمصممين والعارضين الطموحين
so I thought they could be useful.
لذلك اعتقدت أنها قد تكون مفيدة.
These are great.
هذه رائعة.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Also,
أيضًا،
you have any connections with Komiyama's family?
هل لديك أي صلة بعائلة كومياما؟
No.
لا.
Her parents have passed away,
لقد توفي والداها
and her older sister died a few years ago, leaving a son behind.
وتوفيت أختها الكبرى منذ سنوات قليلة، وتركت وراءها ابنًا.
And she was single.
وكانت عازبة.
I see.
أرى.
I thought it'd be helpful to meet them.
اعتقدت أنه سيكون من المفيد مقابلتهم.
Okay. Thanks.
حسنًا، شكرًا.
Wait, isn't today Hinako's thing?
انتظر، أليس اليوم هو يوم هيناكو؟
It is, isn't it?
إنه كذلك، أليس كذلك؟
She hasn't checked in with me yet.
لم تتواصل معي بعد.
I wonder how it's going.
أتساءل كيف تسير الأمور.
Hey, you got a second?
مهلا، هل لديك ثانية؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I overheard you talking, you're a reporter for the Sengoku Weekly, right?
لقد سمعتك تتحدث، أنت مراسل لصحيفة سينجوكو الأسبوعية، أليس كذلك؟
Are you staking out a celebrity or something?
هل أنت تراقب أحد المشاهير أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
I'm not doing that.
انا لا افعل ذلك.
Sorry, but I hate the Sengoku Weekly.
آسف، ولكنني أكره مجلة Sengoku Weekly.
You guys ended my favorite idol's career.
لقد أنهيتم مسيرة فناني المفضل.
How about that?
ماذا عن ذلك؟
-That's not… -What?
-هذا ليس... -ماذا؟
You're a tabloid reporter.
أنت مراسل صحفي.
I don't know what your deal is, but I'm looking for a husband.
لا أعرف ما هي الصفقة الخاصة بك، ولكنني أبحث عن زوج.
You need to leave.
يجب عليك المغادرة.
I'm telling reception there's a tabloid reporter here.
أنا أخبر الاستقبال أن هناك مراسلًا صحفيًا هنا.
Please wait!
انتظر من فضلك!
This is payback for ending my idol.
هذا هو الانتقام لإنهاء معبودي.
I'm not the type of reporter after some gossip.
أنا لست من النوع الذي يبحث عن المراسلين بعد بعض الشائعات.
I just work for Sengokusha's free PR zine.
أنا أعمل فقط في مجلة العلاقات العامة المجانية الخاصة بـ Sengokusha.
So that's the type of lie that you tell?
إذن هذا هو نوع الكذب الذي تقوله؟
I have proof!
لدي دليل!
Sengokusha puts out more than just a tabloid.
لا يقتصر دور سينجوكوشا على نشر الصحف الصفراء فحسب.
We publish interviews like this too.
نحن ننشر مقابلات مثل هذه أيضًا.
I'm just here as a woman who works at a publisher.
أنا هنا فقط كإمرأة تعمل في دار نشر.
Not for an assignment!
ليس للمهمة!
I'm glad you understand.
يسعدني أنك تفهم.
Ms. Shinoda?
السيدة شينودا؟
Yes!
نعم!
So your name is Hinako Shinoda.
إذن اسمك هو هيناكو شينودا.
Who's Makiko Tanioka then?
من هي ماكيكو تانيوكا إذن؟
That reminds me, it did seem like you didn't buy your own ticket.
هذا يذكرني، يبدو الأمر كما لو أنك لم تشترِ تذكرتك بنفسك.
I got it from a friend.
لقد حصلت عليه من صديق.
Yeah?
نعم؟
Makiko Tanioka is the same name as a victim of those suspicious deaths.
ماكيكو تانيوكا هو نفس اسم إحدى ضحايا تلك الوفيات المشبوهة.
Don't tell me.
لا تخبرني.
That's the deal then?
هذه هي الصفقة إذن؟
You used a murder victim's ticket to investigate a crime?
هل استخدمت تذكرة ضحية جريمة قتل للتحقيق في جريمة؟
You suck!
أنت تمتص!
You think tabloids can do whatever they want?
هل تعتقد أن الصحف الصفراء قادرة على فعل ما تريد؟
You're on the wrong path as a human for using a dead woman's name tag.
أنت على الطريق الخطأ كإنسان لاستخدامك بطاقة اسم امرأة ميتة.
Could you not tell people I'm a reporter?
هل يمكنك أن لا تخبر الناس بأنني صحفي؟
I bet you're numb to it already.
أراهن أنك مخدر بالفعل.
You're a piece of trash with no empathy.
أنت قطعة من القمامة وليس لديك أي تعاطف.
Stop looking at your watch.
توقف عن النظر إلى ساعتك.
I mean, Tanioka's case hinges on Ms. Shinoda right now.
أعني أن قضية تانيوكا تتوقف على السيدة شينودا الآن.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
I got some new info.
لقد حصلت على بعض المعلومات الجديدة.
The place where Harue Komiyama and Kubozuka met
المكان الذي التقى فيه هارو كومياما وكوبوزوكا
was a cave bar in Akasaka.
كان بار كهف في أكاساكا.
A cave bar?
بار الكهف؟
The concept is that it's cool in summer and warm in winter.
المفهوم هو أنه بارد في الصيف ودافئ في الشتاء.
Where'd you get this info?
من أين حصلت على هذه المعلومات؟
I got a tentative ID match from the bartender.
لقد حصلت على تطابق هوية مبدئي من النادل.
Got it.
فهمتها.
-Keep going in this direction. -Okay.
-استمر في هذا الاتجاه. -حسنًا.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Hello, Hinako?
مرحباً هيناكو؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Are you at the office?
هل أنت في المكتب؟
I'm at Palazzo Ducale AZABU for work.
أنا في Palazzo Ducale AZABU للعمل.
Wait, I was there last week for a hula dance lesson.
انتظر، كنت هناك الأسبوع الماضي لدرس رقص الهولا.
You came all the way from Chiba? Sorry!
هل أتيتَ من تشيبا؟ معذرةً!
A famous instructor came to teach a lesson, so I joined.
لقد جاء مدرس مشهور لتدريس درس، لذلك انضممت إليه.
It's hard to keep up if you're not regularly exercising.
من الصعب مواكبة ذلك إذا لم تمارس التمارين الرياضية بانتظام.
My legs were jelly.
ساقاي كانتا جيلاتينيتين.
The instructor said "That's not hula dancing, that's dizzy dancing!"
قال المدرب "هذا ليس رقص الهولا، هذا رقص الدوار!"
The whole class was cracking up.
كان الفصل بأكمله ينهار.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
You listening?
هل تستمع؟
Yeah, I am.
نعم انا كذلك.
So, what did you want?
إذن ماذا تريد؟
Your dad and I are coming to Tokyo and wanted to grab dinner.
أنا وأبوك قادمان إلى طوكيو وأردنا تناول العشاء.
Okay, let me know when you pick a date.
حسنًا، أخبرني عندما تختار تاريخًا.
What are you doing there anyway?
ماذا تفعل هناك على أية حال؟
You're not on another stakeout, are you?
أنت لست في مهمة مراقبة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
It's not a stakeout.
إنها ليست عملية مراقبة.
I'm investigating undercover.
أنا أقوم بالتحقيق متخفيا.
What? An undercover investigation?!
ماذا؟ تحقيق سري؟!
Get it together, Hinako!
اجمعيها معًا، هيناكو!
You're working for a publisher!
أنت تعمل لدى ناشر!
Only Tom Cruise and Jack Bauer are allowed to go undercover.
يُسمح فقط لـ توم كروز وجاك باور بالتنقل بشكل سري.
You're a young woman.
أنت امرأة شابة.
Another weird analogy?
تشبيه غريب آخر؟
But I get it.
ولكنني أفهم ذلك.
I'll be fine.
سوف أكون بخير.
Thanks for the call.
شكرا على الاتصال.
Anyway, I gotta get back to work.
على أية حال، يجب أن أعود إلى العمل.
Just call me back later.
فقط اتصل بي لاحقا.
I will.
أنا سوف.
Bye.
الوداع.
LET'S TALK COME TO THE CHAPEL
دعونا نتحدث تعال إلى الكنيسة
It's from Niko-chan!
إنها من نيكو تشان!
You wrote this note?
أنت كتبت هذه المذكرة؟
I'm sorry for the theatrics.
أنا آسف على المسرحية.
I just assume Niko-chan was a--
أفترض فقط أن نيكو تشان كان--
I just have some visual impairments that makes me sensitive to light.
لدي فقط بعض الإعاقات البصرية التي تجعلني حساسًا للضوء.
Would it be okay if I kept my sunglasses on?
هل سيكون من المقبول أن أبقي نظارتي الشمسية على رأسي؟
Yes, of course.
نعم بالطبع.
Am I right to assume your ticket was originally Ms. Tanioka's?
هل من الصحيح أن أفترض أن تذكرتك كانت في الأصل للسيدة تانيوكا؟
That's what I was told.
هذا ما قيل لي.
Have you been entrusted with something other than the ticket?
هل تم تكليفك بشيء آخر غير التذكرة؟
I thought that was you.
اعتقدت أن هذا أنت.
If you have an envelope, could I see it?
إذا كان لديك ظرف، هل يمكنني رؤيته؟
An envelope?
ظرف؟
It's just a regular envelope.
إنه مجرد ظرف عادي.
Sorry.
آسف.
One second.
ثانية واحدة.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
You're Hinako Shinoda?
هل أنت هيناكو شينودا؟
Yes, that's me.
نعم، هذا أنا.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
But I think it's a man.
لكن أعتقد أنه رجل.
Is someone there?
هل هناك أحد؟
Could I see the envelope?
هل يمكنني رؤية الظرف؟
One second.
ثانية واحدة.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Where are you right now?
أين أنت الآن؟
The yard? The main hall?
الفناء؟ القاعة الرئيسية؟
Um, so who am I speaking to?
إذن من الذي أتحدث إليه؟
Does Niko-chan ring a bell?
هل يرن نيكو تشان الجرس؟
Huh?
هاه؟
-What?! -Give me the envelope, now!
-ماذا؟! -أعطني الظرف الآن!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Stop it!
اوقفها!
Tell me where you are now!
أخبرني أين أنت الآن!
Is this it?
هل هذا هو؟
Second floor, the chapel!
الطابق الثاني، الكنيسة!
I'll be taking this.
سوف آخذ هذا.
We're heading downstairs.
نحن نتجه إلى الطابق السفلي.
You said you were visually impaired!
لقد قلت أنك تعاني من ضعف البصر!
He's gone.
لقد رحل.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Oh. I think I found you.
أوه. أعتقد أنني وجدتك.
Are you Ms. Shinoda?
هل أنت السيدة شينودا؟
Are you Niko-chan?
هل أنت نيكو تشان؟
Tanioka and I have been friends since we were teenagers.
لقد كنت أنا وتانيوكا صديقين منذ أن كنا مراهقين.
She had a rough upbringing.
لقد كانت تربيتها صعبة.
She would constantly say how she would marry someone rich.
كانت تقول باستمرار أنها ستتزوج شخصًا غنيًا.
She's the one who found this party and got tickets for us.
إنها هي التي وجدت هذا الحفل وحصلت على التذاكر لنا.
I came to fill the doctor quota.
لقد جئت لملء حصة الطبيب.
DENTIST NIKO-CHAN
طبيب الأسنان نيكو تشان
I was looking forward to today because I like pretty women.
كنت أتطلع إلى اليوم لأنني أحب النساء الجميلات.
But then that happened to Tanioka.
ولكن بعد ذلك حدث ذلك لتانيوكا.
You received her ticket right before she died, right?
لقد حصلت على تذكرتها قبل وفاتها مباشرة، أليس كذلك؟
She told me she didn't need it anymore.
قالت لي أنها لم تعد بحاجة إليه.
She didn't need it?
ولم تكن بحاجة لذلك؟
She said she found the perfect mark.
قالت أنها وجدت العلامة المثالية.
That she won't need to suck up to rich old men anymore
أنها لن تحتاج إلى التملق للرجال الأثرياء المسنين بعد الآن
because she could collect hush money.
لأنها كانت قادرة على جمع المال مقابل الصمت.
I think she found out someone's secret.
أعتقد أنها اكتشفت سر شخص ما.
And then blackmailed them, but…
ثم ابتزهم ولكن...
I should've tried to stop her.
كان ينبغي لي أن أحاول إيقافها.
But she entrusted you with something then, didn't she?
لكنها أوكلت إليك شيئًا حينها، أليس كذلك؟
In case something happened to her?
في حال حدث لها شيء؟
I just met a guy in sunglasses.
لقد قابلت للتو رجلاً يرتدي نظارة شمسية.
That man came to take it!
لقد جاء ذلك الرجل ليأخذها!
Ow.
أوه.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Are you hurt?
هل انت مصاب؟
I'm okay.
انا بخير.
But I'm glad you didn't run into the sunglasses man.
لكنني سعيد لأنك لم تصطدم بالرجل صاحب النظارات الشمسية.
You would've been in danger if he'd seen your face.
لقد كنت في خطر لو رأى وجهك.
Are you really a tabloid reporter?
هل أنت حقا مراسل صحفي؟
Your first instinct was my safety.
غريزتك الأولى كانت سلامتي.
Shouldn't it be to see what Tanioka gave me?
ألا ينبغي أن نرى ما أعطاني إياه تانيوكا؟
I can't believe it.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق ذلك.
I should have some compresses at the clinic.
ينبغي أن أحصل على بعض الكمادات في العيادة.
Let's go get you patched up.
دعنا نذهب لإصلاحك.
FIRST-AID KIT
مجموعة الإسعافات الأولية
So?
لذا؟
I got it on.
لقد حصلت عليه.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Make sure to visit a clinic if the pain doesn't go away.
تأكد من زيارة العيادة إذا لم يختفي الألم.
Okay.
تمام.
Be careful getting back home.
كن حذرا عند العودة إلى المنزل.
Could you tell me about it?
هل يمكنك أن تخبرني عن ذلك؟
What did Ms. Tanioka entrust you with?
ما هي المهمة التي أوكلتها إليك السيدة تانيوكا؟
You really want to know?
هل تريد حقا أن تعرف؟
I do!
أفعل!
What is it that you see with your eyes?
ما الذي تراه بعينيك؟
A scoop, right? You want to know for your article.
معلومة جديدة، أليس كذلك؟ تريد معرفة المزيد لمقالك.
The friends and family of the victims are praying for the truth.
أصدقاء وعائلات الضحايا يصلون من أجل معرفة الحقيقة.
The killer hasn't been caught yet.
لم يتم القبض على القاتل بعد
What can a gossip magazine do?
ماذا تستطيع مجلة الشائعات أن تفعل؟
While I don't trust the cops,
في حين أنني لا أثق في رجال الشرطة،
tabloids are amateurs without any authority.
الصحف الشعبية هي صحف هواة لا تملك أي سلطة.
What exactly can you do with the information?
ماذا يمكنك أن تفعل بالضبط بهذه المعلومات؟
You think tabloids can do whatever they want?
هل تعتقد أن الصحف الصفراء قادرة على فعل ما تريد؟
You're a piece of trash with no empathy.
أنت قطعة من القمامة وليس لديك أي تعاطف.
Buzzing around human misery. Only ever exposing their bad side.
يدور حول معاناة الإنسان، ولا يكشف إلا عن جوانبها السيئة.
That's how you make a living.
هذه هي الطريقة التي تكسب بها عيشك.
You're the worst.
أنت الأسوأ.
Yes, I work for a publisher.
نعم، أنا أعمل لدى ناشر.
It's not my job to pretend to be with the police and arrest criminals.
ليس من وظيفتي أن أتظاهر بأنني مع الشرطة وألقي القبض على المجرمين.
My job is to see the truth about the world with my own eyes and tell the readers!
وظيفتي هي أن أرى الحقيقة حول العالم بأم عيني وأخبر القراء!
What truth about the world?
ما هي الحقيقة حول العالم؟
Celebrities having affairs? An underground idol's true nature?
مشاهير على علاقة غرامية؟ ما هي طبيعة نجم غنائي شهير؟
Nobody cares about that kind of truth.
لا أحد يهتم بهذا النوع من الحقيقة.
Swarming around people's misery, what truth?
التدافع حول بؤس الناس، ما هي الحقيقة؟
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I couldn't say anything the last time this was pointed out.
لم أستطع أن أقول أي شيء عندما تم الإشارة إلى هذا الأمر للمرة الأخيرة.
But there's one thing I know now.
ولكن هناك شيء واحد أعرفه الآن.
The Sengoku Weekly will go after anyone equally!
ستلاحق صحيفة سينجوكو الأسبوعية أي شخص على قدم المساواة!
Even if the target is a powerful politician, a popular athlete,
حتى لو كان الهدف سياسيًا قويًا أو رياضيًا مشهورًا،
or one of our sponsors!
أو أحد رعاتنا!
At the very least, we don't just pick easy targets,
على أقل تقدير، نحن لا نختار الأهداف السهلة فحسب،
we put out anything and everything!
نحن نضع أي شيء وكل شيء!
No matter what the circumstances are!
مهما كانت الظروف!
That's why I think the Sengoku Weekly might be able to do something
لهذا السبب أعتقد أن Sengoku Weekly قد تكون قادرة على فعل شيء ما
to help bring to light
للمساعدة في تسليط الضوء
the truth behind Ms. Tanioka's death!
الحقيقة وراء وفاة السيدة تانيوكا!
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll show you what she gave me.
سأريكم ما أعطتني.
Huh?
هاه؟
TO BE CONTINUED
يتبع
Either way, we have to go hard and fast.
على أية حال، علينا أن نعمل بجد وسرعة.
There's a real person behind the words.
هناك شخص حقيقي وراء الكلمات.
Everyone who got in his way met a tragic fate.
كل من اعترض طريقه لقي مصيرًا مأساويًا.
There's a good chance that's what got her killed.
هناك فرصة جيدة أن هذا هو ما أدى إلى مقتلها.
You mean all three are connected to the case?
هل تقصد أن الثلاثة مرتبطون بالقضية؟
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto
ترجمة الترجمة بواسطة: زينشو ياماموتو